Okay, so it finished and you can see it
ended up creating three files. Now,
every time you run this, it does
something a bit different. That's one of
the bizarre things about this. For you,
it might have only created one file,
index.html. For me, it created three.
And I can click on them to look at them.
This is one file. This is one file. This
is presumably quite a long file. There
it is. And then this is another one, the
stylesheet. So, three files have been
created. They're sitting here in the
directory. And you can see what it
thought about and what it did all the
way over here. Okay, it's time to give
it a try. So, I can look in my file
system at this directory called instant
and we'll see that it has created those
three files. And I can double click on
index.html
to launch this this website. I double
click on it and up comes this arrow keys
to move and turn, space to shoot, neon
arena firsterson shooter. Let's give it
a whirl. Start match. Whoa. Oh, so I am
now controlling. Oh, and I could I could
I could hit this thing and oops, that is
clearly and I I was killed. I'm not much
good at this, but wow, we just have a
firsterson shooter game that was created
out of nothing, doing no work
whatsoever. Now, look, it's entirely
possible that when you ran your one, it
didn't work and something went wrong.
and I'll show you. But then you can just
go back and tell your agent that
something went wrong and it will fix it
for you. But before we do that, I do
think that I should redeem myself by at
least trying to win this and so that I
can a victory. There we go. So that I
can show that I have some some
dexterity. Uh so success. We have been
victorious in this game. And it's pretty
cool that it just worked like that. It
created these files. It coded this game
from just that simple prompt. But let's
see if we can make it a little bit
better. So maybe something didn't work.
Maybe the shooting didn't work.
Sometimes for me that didn't happen.
Once the the keys didn't work at all.
I've tried this a bunch of times and
it's a bit different every time. But
let's suppose we want we want the the
opponent to look a bit more awesome than
just a sphere like that. So So let's
let's prompt here. I'll say that's
great. Um please add some detail
to the opponent.
so that it looks uh more like an enemy.
We'll let it be creative. Uh so that
that is the instruction that we will
give and we will see what comes of this.
So it's now going to uh add some details
and uh you'll see it editing and
changing and I'll come back in a second
when it's ready for us to test it out
again. Okay. Well, it tells us that it's
it's done that. So now let's go back.
Let's double click on index again. Here
we have it. Oh, there indeed is a
slightly more interesting enemy. Uh, and
I I I won again. I'm I'm I'm good at
this game. It's an easy game. Okay.
Well, let's go and do some more edits to
the game. All right. So, back we go.
We'll say, please add a heads up display
HD and also make the
difficulty harder.
uh see what it makes of this. I'll let
it do its planning next moves and its
thinking. We will go through in more
detail at some point about the the
planning and then executing on these
kinds of ideas. And I will see you in a
second when it's finished its work.
Okay, it claims again that it is done
our bidding. Let's see. Let's bring up
this. Here we have it. Start match.
Okay, it uh
it certainly seems more difficult. All
right, it it achieved that goal. Very
nice. So, there you have it. There you
see a very unbusiness-like example of
how quick and easy it is to have an LLM,
a language model, be our agent writing
code with us. It incursor, we had this
conversation with the agent. It created
these three files that are now in
instant. And by iterating, by adding
some more comments, we were able to sort
of work hand in hand at building this
out without writing a single line of
code. And it worked great. And if this
didn't work out for you, if it didn't
work, then please do come back and
iterate. And if if you get stuck and
you're not able to get through some
point, then just delete the whole
instant uh directory and start again.
Create a new instant and and give it a
second shot. Try different model options
and try different ways to prompt it.
This is great experimenting. This is not
an important project. This is just for
you to get a first feel for it. We will
be doing so much of this in the next few
weeks until you are great at it. But
now, let me show you one more thing.
Over the next 3 weeks, we're going to be
using a number of different techniques
to get more and more sophisticated at
working handinhand with AI agents to
build complicated projects. And I
decided to put some of those techniques
to the test. I used a technique called
Ralph loops with Claude code to do this
same project. And I did what what people
sometimes call zero shot, which is I
just set it off. I didn't give it any
feedback. It was one iteration, one
prompt only in this thing called a Ralph
loop that we will cover. And this is the
result of it. Let me show you what it
came up with now. Okay. I'm going to
double click on index.html. All right.
Well, that looks cool. This is the entry
screen. I'll make this nice and big so
you can see it fully. Uh, let's start a
game. Fights, it says. Check this out.
Look at that gun. Look at that. Oh my
goodness. Oh,
try not to get too distracted by this.
Look at his energy. There we go. I won.
Uh, and you can see my my uh uh health
and my kills up at the top. And you can
see the map on the bottom right. Do you
see that? That that little display
there. It's absolutely amazing. And
there's a health over here. I can go and
get a health to recover quickly. Uh
there we go. Uh so this I will stop
playing. That's that's not the point of
this. Uh this is just to give you that
that teaser, that example of what it's
like to go pro with this tool set. This
is using Ralph loops, something that we
will cover, and it's using claw code to
build out a whole application like this.
But again, the thing to bear in mind is
that this is something where I just
typed in a prompt and let it go. I
didn't give it any feedback and it came
up with this which which I think is
really cool and this is something that
you'll be able to do too in just a
matter of days. All right, so that
concludes the instant gratification. I
hope that you feel gratified. That was a
lot of fun. From this point on, it's all
business. We'll be building commercial
stuff and we're going to start by
actually discussing what this course is
all about.